(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-30T04:29:02.007701",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
震える星の
Of the trembling stars,
ただ触れて抱きしめていたいような
wanting just to touch and hold them close,
特急 暗い夜のそこで
express, at the bottom of the dark night,
少し楽しんで なんてね
enjoying it a bit... just kidding.
チョーデンパ的 巡って丸ごとキャッチと
Super radio-wave style, catching it whole,
空の彼方へ とんでとんで
flying far beyond the sky, flying away,
大体鳴らしてる 胸踊るスパギガのね
Playing proudly, my heart dances to the super giga,
あたん、チュッ、ラリラリ、弾けこね先の未来
Atan, chu, rari rari, the future bursting ahead,
誰もが求めるウェロね
everyone's desired well-o-ne,
チョーデンパ的 巡って丸ごとキャッチと
Super radio-wave style, catching it whole,
空の彼方へ とんでとんで
flying far beyond the sky, flying away,
探せるまでのさ
until I can find it...
まだ見たことない未来を とんでとんでそれ
flying to a yet unseen future, flying away,
証明する チョコがばりさんでんぱ
Proving it with chocolate barisandempa,
飛び込む ヘリかるまいのおら
jumping into the helicopter-like...
この夢革命コードでさ 特等席を飛び跳ねて 見せるにゅわ
with this dream-revolutionary code, jumping to the front row, I'll show you,
ひとりじゃいけないところまで
to a place we can't reach alone,
連れて行ってくれるよね
you'll take me there, won't you?
さあ 時代を超えて
Now, transcending eras,
さあ 次はどこへ
now, where to next?
さあ 巡り続け ストリングをかけて
Now, continuing to wander, pulling the strings,
チョーデンパ的 想像できるさいむさのメモリー
Super radio-wave style, imagining memories of saimusa,
その夢は ここに 今
that dream is right here, right now,
チョーデンパ的 巡って丸ごとキャッチと
Super radio-wave style, catching it whole,
空の彼方へとんでとんで
flying far beyond the sky,
チョーデンパ的 巡って丸ごとキャッチと えんとなビートに身を任せ
leaving it to the enchanting beat,
イフィニティの先へ
beyond infinity!
探せるまでのさ ゼミのロカルタセンテ
until I can find it, seminar local sentence,
まだ見たことない未来をとんでとんでそれ
flying to a yet unseen future, flying away,
チョーデンパ的 巡って丸ごとキャッチと
Super radio-wave style, catching it whole,
地平を超えて 人の中の聖域へ 絶対マジック
Crossing the horizon, into the sanctuary within people, absolute magic!
君と明かす夜　明日もまた同じ
...With you, another night will fall.
朝日が昇るなら
As the sun rises again...
もう！
No more!
青く光る夜が　星空の未来を
...Another bright night will come.
さあ、おお！
So...
私を照らして
I'll illuminate myself,
タップで地球を揺らすくらい
Rocking the earth so much.
ここで踊り明かそう
Let's dance here!
午前5時の夜明けの街で
In the town at 5:00 AM...
なんか一人ぼっちな気分　薄れていくパレット
Feeling so lonely, slipping away.
ぼんやり眺める　ベッド別々期待してさ
Gazing vaguely, waiting side by side...
君の足音
Your footsteps.
触れたっても　触れられないし
Even if we touch, we can't connect.
運命の浅い糸なんて知るなし
Not knowing such a deep fate...
それでも君と繋がっていたい
Still, I want to connect with you.
明るくなる空に　この思いのせても
By the brightening sky, holding these feelings...
何も見えない
No matter what, nothing shows.
灰色に流るむ　雲間から差し込む
Flowing into the shadows, piercing through the clouds.
タイミングとかさ
Such timing...
たっぷり深呼吸して　境界線を越える
Taking a deep breath, crossing boundaries.
痛む痛みへ　至る場所
To a place of pain...
裸足で踊る　夜の街並み
Dancing barefoot, wandering through the night.
きらきら光るの
Shining brightly!
ねえ　早く気づいて
Realize it quickly...
Let's go, let's stop.
朝日が昇るなら
...As the sun rises again.
もう！
No more!
青く光る夜が　星空の未来を
...Another bright night will come.
さあ、おお！
So...
私を照らして
I'll illuminate myself,
タップで地球を揺らすくらい
Rocking the earth so much.
ここで踊り明かそう
Let's dance here!
なんであなたにはできないの？
Why can't I do it for you?
なんてさ　陰口言われたり諦められたり　好感度下がる手前で
Saying mean things, getting rejected, dropping in rank.
列車は私を置き去りにしちゃうし
Leaving the train behind...
刃物の野菜もスピード早すぎだね
Sharp vegetables too, the speed is too fast!
針のままの軌跡じゃ足りないんだ　Take me!
Just the current traces aren't enough, take me!
毎日死ぬほど頑張ってやっとここまで連れてきたんだ
Working hard enough to die every day, I finally brought you here!
あなたにはわからない
I can't understand you.
わかってほしいくらい
I want you to understand.
私の苦労も雲もどうかご存じないで
Don't know my hardships and clouds.
いてね
Just stay!
きっとあなたにもできるはず
Surely you can do it too.
なんてさ　言うほど無責任にはなりたくない
I don't want to be as irresponsible as that!
それでも死ぬほど頑張って書ける寝落ちはあると思った
Even so, I thought there's room to write if I try hard enough to die...
投げ出しくたなるとよ
I want to throw it all away...
でも諦めたくはない
Even so, I don't want to give up.
私の未来も失敗も全部私だけのもの
My future too, I gave you all my failures, but...
あなたにはわからない
I can't understand you.
わかってほしいくらい
I want you to understand.
私の苦労も雲もどうかご存じないで
Don't know my hardships and clouds.
いてね
Just stay!
一度きりの私の物語は
My one-and-only story
運命を超えて煌めくんだ 行こう
shines beyond fate. Let's go.
ねぇ私より 私のことわかってくれるキミの存在が
Hey, your existence, which understands me better than I do myself,
懦弱で泣き虫な心に勇気と言う魔法をかけたの
cast a magic called courage upon my cowardly, crybaby heart.
チクタク 時計の針だけが進む 立ち止まってちゃダメだ ソラ 転び八起きがお決まりでしょ
Tick-tock, only the hands of the clock move. You can't stand still, Sora. "Falling seven times, getting up eight" is the norm, right?
さあ
Now...
胸に詰め込んだ 夢はくしゃくしゃで
With dreams stuffed in my chest all crumpled up,
勇気がいるけど キミにだけは見せよっとだから
and though I need courage, I'll show it only to you, so
一緒に行けるかな キミの街を渡してこう
can we go together? Handing you my town,
深呼吸して 胸の鼓動を高めたこと
taking a deep breath, raising the beat in my chest,
ライブで笑っちゃおうフライハイ
let's laugh it off in the live show, fly high!
一つ一つ重ねてきた想いを キミとこうして語り合えたらなんて嘘みたいだな
It feels like a lie to be able to talk with you like this about the feelings we've built one by one.
もっとまたたいてしるして
Shine even brighter, leave your mark,
最初の一歩とうまくいかないよだって教科書で歌った
Even if the first step doesn't go well, the textbook sang,
明日の教科書 水にしたらなんだってやれそうだ
if tomorrow's textbook becomes water, it feels like we can do anything.
落書きの中 生きてた思いを
The feelings that lived inside the graffiti,
キミとこうして分かち合えたらなんて嘘みたいだな
if we could share them with you like this, it feels like a lie.
もっとまたたいてしるして 楽しかった日々ほら 一瞬で過ぎていくの
Shine even brighter, leave your mark. Look, these fun days pass by in an instant,
昨日のようにも加速してる ちゃんと繋いでて
accelerating just like yesterday, hold my hand tight.
最初の一歩とうまくいかないよだって教科書で歌った
Even if the first step doesn't go well, the textbook sang,
明日の教科書 水にしたらなんだってやれそうだ
if tomorrow's textbook becomes water, it feels like we can do anything.
落書きの中 生きてた思いを
The feelings that lived inside the graffiti,
キミとこうして分かち合えたらなんて嘘みたいだな
if we could share them with you like this, it feels like a lie.
もっとまたたいてしるして 楽しかった日々ほら 一瞬で過ぎていくの
Shine even brighter, leave your mark. Look, these fun days pass by in an instant,
昨日のようにも加速してる ちゃんと繋いでて
accelerating just like yesterday, hold my hand tight.
簡単じゃないホームの掛け声は いつもキミが明るく放って支えてくれるずっと
The cheers of a home that isn't easy—you always cheerfully send them out and support me forever.
刻まれて光るよ
They are engraved and shine bright.
一つ一つ重ねてきた 未来地図のページをめくるように
Like turning the pages of a future map we've layered one by one,
消えてしまうけど それと同じで
though they fade away, just like that,
キミの顔ばかり 浮かべてたら
when I keep picturing only your face,
愛すみたいに届けては
delivering it like love...
どんなふうになる
How will it turn out?
夢も愛もギュッとしていっぱいだから文字切れない
Dreams and love are packed so full, I can't express it all,
でも欲張りすぎてきっとしていく
But being too greedy, I'll surely keep going...
もなかなかちゅうちょ恋に落ちちゃって
Hesitantly, I've fallen in love,
戻れない あれあれなんでふわりと
I can't turn back. Oh oh, why so softly
心がまだ熱くなるのなかなかちゅうちょ君の重力で
Does my heart still grow hot? Hesitantly, by your gravity,
引き寄せて
Drawing me in,
きらめくの未来見たいわからない
The shimmering future I want to see, I don't know.
未来見たいわからない
The future I want to see, I don't know.
あーアップダウンで超振り回す
Ah, up and down, completely swinging me around,
弱音で今日は終始六時中
Complaining all the time, 24/7 today,
カレンダー30日でも足りないあれもこれもそれも全部したい
Even a 30-day calendar isn't enough, I want that, this, and everything!
ギュンギュンキュン上昇 特異的発酵
Heart-pounding ascent, unique fermentation,
ギュンギュンキュン交差 深呼吸
Heart-pounding intersection, deep breath,
ギュンギュンキュン上昇 ラブルメーター
Heart-pounding ascent, love meter,
ギュンギュンキュン交差 突っ切って行こう!
Heart-pounding intersection, let's break through!
無限大の愛だけど
Even though it's infinite love,
しいっぽいだけど諦めない
it's painful, but I won't give up,
まだ欲張りだから君と落ちていく
I'm still greedy, so I'll fall with you.
もなかなかちゅうちょ心がハマって抜け出せない
Hesitantly, my heart gets hooked and I can't escape.
あれあれなんでねまぶしい心がまだ熱くなるの
Oh oh, why is it dazzling? My heart is still getting hot.
もなかなかちゅうちょスピード重視で引き寄せて
Hesitantly, prioritizing speed, drawing me in.
きらめくの未来見たいわからない
The shimmering future I want to see, I don't know.
一歩踏み出だせば 勇気を出して
If I take a step forward, gathering courage,
私はまだ未完成で あの空に目を染めてしまうんだ
I'm still incomplete, dyeing my eyes in that sky.
考えても どうしようもないことだとか 求めたら
Even if I think about it, there's nothing I can do, or if I seek it,
心からいろいろ感てくるけど だからこそ
It comes feeling various things from the heart, but precisely because of that,
笑顔でね だからこそ負けないで
With a smile, precisely because of that, don't lose.
羽ばたくための翼を手にして 飛び出してくんだよ
Taking wings to flutter and soar out!
空を飛んでいこう 飛んでいこう 色づいてく夢ほら道すがら
Let's fly through the sky, fly through, dreams coloring along the way,
青混ぜてみよう 混ぜてみよう 少し大きくなったね
Let's mix blue, mix blue, it got a bit bigger.
空は青い色 青い色
The sky is blue, blue color,
少し迷ったらすぐに夜空色
If you get a little lost, right away night sky color,
ちょっと迷っても 迷っても ゆっくり風を受けて
Even if you get a little lost, slowly receiving the wind.
空を飛んでいこう 飛んでいこう 青い色 影の色
Let's fly through the sky, fly through, blue color, layered color...
いつしか忘れていた奇跡の形をさ
The shape of the miracle we once forgot...
あるときは笑顔でね あるときは涙を
At times with a smile, at times with tears...
見上げた空だつて ねじしにして飛び出してくんだよ届けて
The sky we looked up at, making it a screw, soaring out and delivering it!
空はくらい色 影の色
The sky is dark color, shadow color...
私がきっとばればれにしちゃうから空のかたち色
I'll surely make it bare, the sky's shape and color...
無限の果て いつかまったこの場所でどんな空色が見えるかな
At the infinite end, in this place we waited, what sky color can we see?
バーチャル？リアル？どっちかわいい？
Virtual? Real? Which is cute?
バーチャル？リアル？どっちカワイイ？
バーチャル？リアル？どっち可愛い？
Virtual? Real? Which is cute?
バーチャルリアルどっちもかわいい
Virtual, real, both are cute.
check it, ちゅきちゅきちゅるっchu
Check it, chu-ki-chu-ki-chu-ru-t-chu,
チェリチェリーチューインチュインちょ
cherry, cherry, chewing, chu-in-cho,
色づき始めた夢は止まらない
the dreams that started to color won't stop,
夢は止まらない
the dream won't stop,
もっと伝えよう 伝えよう
let's convey it more, convey it more,
ラララ どんなメロディで
la la la, with what kind of melody?
空は青い色 青い色
The sky is blue, blue.
サムネタップはじめて きゅんきゅんってしたなら
Thumbnail tap for the first time, if it fluttered,
すぐに優しい色 青い色 そっと恋しくって
quickly a gentle blue color, softly longing,
手を取り合って笑い合ってくれるなら
If you hold my hand and share a smile with me,
これからもあたしのことよろしくね
please take care of me from now on too,
今日の日を朗らかに歌いながら 飛んでいこう
cheerfully singing today's day, let's fly away!
バーチャルリアル どっちかわいい？
Virtual, real, which is cute?
バーチャルリアル どっちもかわいい！
Virtual, real, both are cute!
check it ちゅきちゅきちゅるっchu
Check it, chu-ki-chu-ki-chu-ru-t-chu!
サムネタップはじめて きゅんきゅんってしたなら ハート押して
Thumbnail tap, if your heart flutters, press the heart.
通知はon いつでもcome on 一緒に踊ろうよ on and on
Notifications on, always come on, let's dance together on and on.
お菓子食べたいけどダイエット中 キミの好みにアップデート中
I want to eat snacks, but I'm on a diet, updating to your preferences.
キミと更新 もっと推してほしいの
Updating with you, I want you to support me more.
バーチャル リアル どっちが好き？ つながる1、2、3次元
Virtual, real, which do you like? Connecting 1, 2, 3 dimensions,
ワンツー３で飛び越えて 今やネットもリアルです
one, two, three, jumping over them, now the internet is real too.
チクチクしないで ラブとピースで ときめいちゃう時かけgirl
Don't be prickly, with love and peace, a heart-fluttering time-travel girl.
2Dプラス3Dは 混ぜれば最強 バーチャルアールラブ
2D plus 3D is, if you mix them, the strongest VirtuaReal Love.
つきたすセリリングは 待てれば最高 バーチャルアールラブ
Adding ceiling is best if you can wait, VirtuaReal Love.
check it ちゅきちゅきちゅるっchu
Check it, chu-ki-chu-ki-chu-ru-t-chu!
2番にスワイプ beat足して きゅんきゅんってしたなら 手叩いて
Swipe to number 2, add beat, if it flutters, clap your hands.
お姉の願いは一緒だけど コラボ中 新しいことリサーチ中
My wish is the same, but collaborating, researching new things.
ぴいぴいぴいテレパシー 今日も配信 もっとハート欲しいの
Pi-pi-pi telepathy, streaming today too, I want more hearts.
ねぇねぇ どっちかわいい？ どっちかわいい？
Hey hey, which is cute? Which is cute?
どっちかわいい？ どっちかわいい？ どっちかわいい？
Which is cute? Which is cute? Which is cute?
ねぇねぇ どっちかわいい？ どっちかわいい？
Hey hey, which is cute? Which is cute?
どっちかわいい？ どっちかわいい？ どっちかわいい？ どっちもかわいい！
Which is cute? Which is cute? Which is cute? Both are cute!
お菓子食べたいけどダイエット中
I want to eat snacks, but I'm on a diet,
キミの好みにアップデート中 キミと更新 もっと推してほしいの
updating to your preferences, updating with you, I want you to support me more.
バーチャル リアル どっちが好き？ つながる1、2、3次元
Virtual, real, which do you like? Connecting 1, 2, 3 dimensions,
ワンツー３で飛び越えて 今やネットもリアルです
one, two, three, jumping over them, now the internet is real too.
チクチクしないで ラブとピースで ときめいちゃう時かけgirl
Don't be prickly, with love and peace, a heart-fluttering time-travel girl.
2Dプラス3Dは 混ぜれば最強 バーチャルアールラブ
2D plus 3D is, if you mix them, the strongest VirtuaReal Love.
つきたすセリリングは 待てれば最高 バーチャルアールラブ
Adding ceiling is best if you can wait, VirtuaReal Love.
check it ちゅきちゅきちゅるっchu
Check it, chu-ki-chu-ki-chu-ru-t-chu!
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a moment until the show starts.
ときのそら 8th Starry Bloomin' Anniversary Party
Tokino Sora 8th Starry Bloomin' Anniversary Party
しばらくお待ちください。
Please stand by.
Please wait a moment.
君に捧げる青空には
To the blue sky dedicated to you,
始まりの強がりから
from the bravado of the beginning,
本当は触れている 手足が震えないよう
I'm actually touching, so my hands and feet won't tremble.
もう出来上がりの先はどこ？
Where is beyond the finished product?
気まぐれな色願いが
A capricious color wish
癖になりかけたころ
became a habit just as
やめられない変な色のことよ
it became an unquenchable, strange color.
蝶々みたいに跳ねて 飛べたらいいのに
I wish I could flutter and fly like a butterfly.
もう何もいらないから 壊れちゃいたくないから
Because I don't need anything else, because I don't want to break,
どこまでも遠くへと
to the far reaches anywhere,
子供みたいに泣いて 泣きじゃくるように
crying like a child, sobbing away,
あの闇を超えて 秘密の地図を探して
crossing that darkness, searching for a secret map.
もっともっと遠くへと
further, further away,
手の届く場所へと行こう
let's go to a place within reach.
なくしたものはみつかった？
Did you find what you lost?
見失いかけた切り出しじゃんか
It's just a losing start we almost missed.
いつのまにか傷ついた
Before we knew it, we were hurt,
君のスペシャルな夢のすね
on your special dream's...
子供みたいに愛して 願うからいいのに
Loving like a child, even though wishing is fine,
気をつけて 森の中へと
be careful, into the forest,
でも すべて抱きしめて
but embrace everything,
オラクルはきっと大事なものだから 離れても 探しても 離れないでよ
because the oracle is surely something important, so even if we part, even if we search, don't leave me.
空の果て 雲の向こう
at the end of the sky, beyond the clouds,
この先を見つめて 恋みたいに このいのち違って
gazing at what lies ahead, like love, living this life differently.
もう何もいらないから 忘れさせてあげる
Because I don't need anything else, I'll let you forget.
どこまでも遠くへ
To faraway places...
ありのまま進んで
Moving forward just as I am,
波を越えて 青闇を越えて
Crossing waves, crossing the blue darkness,
いつだって宇宙までいよいよ
Always getting closer to outer space,
行こう
Let's go.
ユートピアのルーツの空へ
To the sky at the roots of utopia.
高鳴る心臓に緑を乗せて
Placing green upon my pounding heart,
曖昧な夢を描く
Drawing vague dreams.
幻想は外のまま 終われらないんだ
Reality remains outside, unable to be finished—
答えをずっと探して続けて
Continually searching for the answer,
何者かになりたくて
Wanting to become someone,
酸いも甘いも流した理由をただ探して
Just searching for the reason I shed bitter and sweet tears.
優しく寄り添って 心が晴れるのなら
If snuggling close gently clears my heart,
翼が生えたようね
It's like wings have sprouted.
逃げ出して矛盾だらけの世界に飛び込んで
Running away and diving into a world full of contradictions,
だって言葉にして伝えたその時が最初で最後だ
Because the moment I put it into words was both the first and last.
世界にありふれた不確かさも僕が消して
I will erase even the common uncertainties of this world,
淀みに咲いた花のように強くいられるように
So I can stay strong like a flower blooming in stagnant water.
小さな光に憧れて
Yearning for a small light...
名前を持たない歌がさ
A song without a name—
神様は認めてくれない
God won't acknowledge it.
一つ一つ枯れない花のように
Like flowers that never wither, one by one.
昨日の自分に頼り出してこぼれた涙も
Even the tears I shed, relying on my past self,
上手に笑えるのなら
If I can smile skillfully,
その日が来たんだ
That day has finally come.
だって理想が飛び交って背中を押したんだよ
Because ideals flew about and pushed me on.
それだけ手を伸ばして叫んだって届かないの
Even if I reach out and shout that much, it doesn't reach.
大人になれば自然と笑って生きられるの
If I become an adult, will I naturally smile and live?
どうか歌うように満ちて
May it fill me as if singing.
木の戸まりばっか足がすくんで立てないよ
My feet are stuck on closed doors, unable to stand.
音のない世界から君を見つけて連れ出して
Find me from a soundless world and lead me away.
言葉紡いで歌うことが
Weaving words and singing
私の運命だ
Is my destiny.
世界にありふれた不確かさも僕が消して
I will erase even the common uncertainties of this world,
淀みに咲いた花のように強くいられるように
So I can stay strong like a flower blooming in stagnant water.
小さな光に憧れて
Yearning for a small light...
その手離さずに誰から
Without letting go of that hand, from anyone...
それでもいい巡り巡る心の空へ
Even so, going round and round to the sky of my heart...
アバンチュールラリラリ 飛び込む
Aventure lari-lari, diving in
海の底へ
to the bottom of the ocean!
アバンチュール 時代巡り
An adventurous era spinning,
巡る魔法
a spinning magic.
宇宙を 走り抜けたら
If we run through the universe,
時代変動こうして
how will the era change?
さあ 色波へ
Now, toward the colorful waves,
さあ 無限大 ロードの可能性へ
now, toward the endless road of possibilities!
飛び出せ ピピピ 巡って
Jump out, pipipi, spinning around
まるごとずっと
and keeping it all,
空の彼方
beyond the sky.
踊れ 踊れ ドレパピピ
Dance, dance, dore-papipi,
巡って 巡ること ずっと
spinning and spinning forever.
空の 彼方 踊れ 踊れ ドレパピピ
Beyond the sky, dance, dance, dore-papipi,
手をつないで インフィニティの先へ
holding hands, heading beyond infinity!
ララララララ ララナラララララ
Lalalalalala laranalalalala
語り継ぐのさ セルカルタ
passing down the Celcarta tales,
ララララララ ララナラララララ
Lalalalalala laranalalalala
片目が凍える ナイトペペ
a frozen single eye, knight pepe!
ララララララ ララナラララララ
Lalalalalala laranalalalala
語り継ぐのさ セルカルタ
passing down the Celcarta tales,
想像する 浄化の先
imagining beyond purification,
チョガが重なり 三次元へ
choga overlapping into three dimensions!
アバンチュール ラリラリ
Aventure lari-lari,
飛び込む 繰り広げる バイナリー
jumping in, unfolding binary!
アバンチュール 発見
Aventure discovery,
巡り巡る ソラ
spinning around the sky.
さらにさらに内に 打たれて
Beaten further within,
見せるのは
what is shown is...
アバンチュール ラリラリ
Aventure lari-lari,
1人じゃ行けない 心の旅
a journey of the heart you can't take alone.
見せて ピピピ 巡る魔法で
Show me, pipipi, with spinning magic.
時代を超えて
Crossing eras,
さあ いわの 声へ
now, toward the voice of the shore,
さあ 巡り 続ける 動きを
now, continue spinning the movements,
飛び出せ ピピピ
jump out, pipipi.
ちょでパピピ 繋がり ドキト君との メロディ
Chode-papipi, connecting, the melody with you and me,
一緒に見たい夢が ここに 今芽生え 始まり始めた
the dream we want to see together is sprouting and beginning right here, right now!
永遠の 鍵へ ちょでパピピ
Toward the key of eternity, chode-papipi,
巡って 巡ること ずっと 空の
spinning and spinning forever, of the sky...
体を ご機嫌 踊る ちょでパピピ
body in a good mood, dancing, chode-papipi,
巡って 巡ること ずっと
spinning and spinning forever,
どこな きずきを またさせ インフィニティの先へ
waiting for some realization, heading beyond infinity!
ララララララ ララナラララララ
Lalalalalala laranalalalala
語り継ぐのさ セルカルタ
passing down the Celcarta tales,
ララララララ ララナラララララ
Lalalalalala laranalalalala
片目が凍える ナイトペペ
a frozen single eye, knight pepe!
それ 少しの
That little bit...
ララララララ ララナラララララ
Lalalalalala laranalalalala
輝きを閉ざしそめて それでもご機嫌
trapping the radiance, yet still in a good mood,
満タンの心で
with a full heart!
はい！みんな、こんばんはー！
Hi everyone, good evening!
みんなの声が大きすぎて、オーケが聞こえのレベルの大完成、ありがとう！
Everyone's voices were so loud, it reached the level of a full orchestra! Thank you so much!
ちょっと、一言キックしてもらっちゃおっかな？
Shall I have you all give a little kick?
ということで、1年半ぶりの「ソロパ」なんですけど、
So, this is my first solo performance in a year and a half,
え、ちょっとこれのやっちゃっていいですか？
um, is it okay if we do this one?
えっと…、せーの…、みんなー！
Um... ready, set... everyone!
って呼んで「はーい！」とか言ってください。
Call out and say "Hi!" like that.
行きますよ！ 男の子ー！
Here we go! Boys!
ちょっと、恥ずかしいかもしれない、ちょっと手だけでも振っていいよ。女の子ー！
You might feel a bit embarrassed, but you can just wave your hands. Girls!
声聞こえてありがとう！
Thank you for letting me hear your voices!
海外の方ー！ すごーい！
People from overseas! That's amazing!
そして、そだな…、めっちゃ遠くから来たよって人、絶対自分が一番遠いみたいな人、いる？
And let's see... people who came from really far away, anyone who thinks they came the absolute furthest? Are there any?
あ、でも海外の方かな？ありがとうございます！
Ah, but maybe overseas people? Thank you very much!
そして、そだな…、ミゼネル席の方ー！ やー、ありがとうございます！
And let's see... people in the Mizenel seats! Yay, thank you so much!
では、みんなで行くよ！ みんなー！ こっちがわー！
Now, let's all go together! Everyone! This side!
こっちがわー！
That side!
最後に、全員ー！ ありがとうー！
Finally, everyone! Thank you!
はい！ 手を繋ぎ… これがね、やりたかったんです、ずっと。
Yes! Holding hands... this is what I wanted to do for so long.
えいっ
Hey!
はい、どーもー！
Hi there, everyone!
というわけでですね、なんと、YouTubeで見てる皆さん！
So, as it turns out, everyone watching on YouTube!
無料配信は、ここまなんです！
The free broadcast ends right here!
え、今来たばかり？
Huh, you just got here?
私も今来たばかり！
I just got here too!
そうだよね、わかるわかる。
Right, I know, I know.
えー、わかってるよ、コメントの皆も見えてるよ。
Um, I get it, I can see everyone in the comments too.
「イェーイ」って言ってるな、イェー
You're saying "Yay," yeah—
うん、ちょっとラグってるのかも知れない。
Hm, it might be lagging a bit.
今来たばかりって書いてね、よろしく（笑）
Make sure to write "Just got here," please! (Laughs)
続きは、えー、見たい人概要欄から見てもらえると。
For the rest, um, those who want to watch can check the description.
どこにあるのか概要欄。
Where is the description, anyway?
どっかに概要欄が多分あるんで、ここらへんからちょっと見てもらえれば
There's probably a description somewhere, so if you check around here...
嬉しいです！
I'd be so happy!
次の曲いっちゃおうかな？
Shall we go to the next song?
おー！
Whoa!
まだまだ盛り上がれる？
Can you guys get even more hyped?
イェーイ！
Yeah!
みんながおうちに帰ってくるの、待ってたよ。
I've been waiting for you all to come back home.
というわけで、次の曲は新アルバムからこの曲です。
So, the next song is this one from the new album.
おー！
Whoa!
Starry Bloomin'!
冒頭無料配信はここで終了です。
The free introductory broadcast ends here.
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。★ライブチケット購入はコチラ★ SPWN
This concludes the free opening stream. Purchase live tickets here: SPWN